<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Breaches on Casey Becking</title>
    <link>http://caseybecking.com/tags/breaches/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Breaches on Casey Becking</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 18:46:57 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://caseybecking.com/tags/breaches/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>You’ve been hacked!  What to do to save your business.</title>
      <link>http://caseybecking.com/post/youve-been-hacked/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 18:46:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caseybecking.com/post/youve-been-hacked/</guid>
      <description>There’s no denying that E-commerce has grown at an enormous rate in the last decade. For many companies, eCommerce has quickly become the fastest growing channel; if not the largest channel of sales. Yet sadly, with growth, come those who’d also like to profit from the hundreds of thousands of unprotected sites, ripe with personal data and payment details. Successful ecommerce platforms, such as Magento with 200,000+ installs, makes for a ripe target for the savvy hacker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Data Breaches of 2015</title>
      <link>http://caseybecking.com/post/2016-08-30-biggest-data-breaches-of-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 18:29:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caseybecking.com/post/2016-08-30-biggest-data-breaches-of-2015/</guid>
      <description>2014 was certainly a big year for data breaches; impacting the likes of Adobe, Apple, Evernote, eBay, and Facebook….to name a few of the headliners. As 2015 came to a close, we saw even more breaches, hitting the likes of industries like health-care, financial, education, federal government, and eCommerce. While the threat of cyber security increases, the good news is that we’re seeing more and more companies getting educated, taking action, and making increased investments in both security technologies and people (CSO), for which to manage threats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>But I run Magento.  I’m small.  Why would I get hacked?</title>
      <link>http://caseybecking.com/post/but-i-run-magento/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 17:39:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://caseybecking.com/post/but-i-run-magento/</guid>
      <description>After working with many small and mid-sized retailers in 2015, there is one thing they all have in common—the assumption that hackers won’t bother with them. Actually it’s the reverse - criminals have figured out small companies are easier to penetrate, and go after them more frequently. Why go for one big hack, of say eBay or Facebook, when you can hack 5,000+ sites which NEVER take notice?
In spite of high-profile hacks such as against Apple, Cisco, or even the US Government, many online retailers still do not believe that they are at risk or have been a victim of undetected hacks by criminal groups.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>