<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Devlopment on Casey Becking</title>
    <link>http://www.caseybecking.com/tags/devlopment/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Devlopment on Casey Becking</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2016. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="http://www.caseybecking.com/tags/devlopment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo to Rackspace using Travis</title>
      <link>http://www.caseybecking.com/post/hugo-to-rackspace-using-travis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 14:19:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.caseybecking.com/post/hugo-to-rackspace-using-travis/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;After reading Evan Browns post &lt;a href=&#34;http://evanbrown.io/post/hugo-on-the-go/&#34;&gt;Hugo on the go&lt;/a&gt; I was inspired to figure out how to do this exact same thing but as opposed to using AWS I wanted to use &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.rackspace.com/cloud/files&#34;&gt;Rackspace Cloud FIles&lt;/a&gt; and more specfically Rackspace Static Website feature, because Rackspace Cloud Files is an inexpensive way to store and distribute objects, the Cloud Files static website feature coupled with the lightning-fast content delivery network (CDN) is a winning combination in terms of both performance and price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Creating a static website—a site that does not change for each request—with Cloud Files and the updated Control Panel is as easy as pointing and clicking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;to-set-up-a-static-webiste-using-the-rackspace-control-panel&#34;&gt;To set up a static webiste using the Rackspace Control Panel&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the Control Panel, you begin to set up your static website by creating a container.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Login to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://mycloud.rackspace.com&#34;&gt;Control Panel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the Files section of the Control Panel, click &lt;strong&gt;Create Container&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fill in a name and a region for your static webite.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For &lt;strong&gt;Type&lt;/strong&gt;, select &lt;strong&gt;Static Website&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;strong&gt;Create Container&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the Control Panel, click on your static website container, and then click the &lt;strong&gt;Upload Files&lt;/strong&gt; button.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the File Upload dialog box, click &lt;strong&gt;Choose Files&lt;/strong&gt; and navigate to the folder with your content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select your content (you can select multiple files), and then click &lt;strong&gt;Open&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the Control Panel, navigate to your container listing by clicking the &lt;strong&gt;Containers&lt;/strong&gt; link.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click the cog wheel next to your static website container, and then click &lt;strong&gt;View All Links&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the CDN URLs for your container are displayed. For HTML pages and pictures, use the HTTP link for your static website container.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;to-set-up-a-automated-deployments-using-travis-ci&#34;&gt;To set up a Automated Deployments using Travis CI&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again my &lt;em&gt;.travis.yml&lt;/em&gt; file was very similar to Evan Browns except im using a few pieces to talk to rackspace&amp;rsquo;s cloud -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34;&gt;language: go                                                                                                                                  
go:
- 1.4
install:
- go get github.com/spf13/hugo
script: hugo
before_deploy: cd public
deploy:
  provider: cloudfiles
  username: RACKSPACE USERNAME
  api_key:
    secure: APIKEYFROMRACKSPACE
  region: REGION
  container: CONTAINERNAME
  skip_cleanup: true
  on:
    repo: caseyCaseybecking/www_caseybecking_com_hugo
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Login to the Control Panel and goto &lt;strong&gt;Account Settings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under &lt;strong&gt;Login Details&lt;/strong&gt; you will see &lt;strong&gt;API KEY&lt;/strong&gt; - Copy That&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/travis-ci/travis.rb&#34;&gt;Travis CLI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CD into your current hugo working directory&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute &lt;code&gt;travis setup cloudfiles&lt;/code&gt;
&lt;em&gt;This will ask you a few questions for setup and create the &lt;em&gt;.travis.yml&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once this file is created you can push it to your repo (modification may be needed).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now withing Travis you should be able to view the repo within &lt;em&gt;My Repositories&lt;/em&gt; flip the switch so it is enabled and it should try to build.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>